嘿，你们好，我是TheCherno，欢迎回到我的游戏引擎系列教程
hey, look guys my name is TheCherno, welcome back to my game engine series
那么上期看了Github和Hazel，以及它们的工作流，如果你们还没看过，一定要去看看那期
so last time we took a look at github and Hazel and how all of that kind of work, definitely check out that video, if you haven't already
因为实际上我们今天会继续看Github，并且也会了解一下合并请求
because today we're actually going to be continuing on with the whole github thing and taking a look at pull requests
当然除了看看它们，今天也会整合其中一些和并请求
and apart from just taking a look at them and integrating some of them today
我们还将讨论将来如何通过进行合并请求协作
we're also going to discuss how in the future you should collaborate via pull requests
所以我认为这对每个人来说都是一个非常有用的主题，在Hazel项目之外，也会非常有用
so I think this is like a really useful topic for everyone, it's also gonna be very useful outside of Hazel
因为如果你们在使用Github，如果你在与一群人一起工作，并且在使用git
because if you're working with github, if you're working with kind of teams of people and you're using git
并且邀请您真正使用合并请求的版本控制系统并不重要
and invite it doesn't really matter what version control system you're really using pulled requests
就是能够，你们知道，作为一个团队创建代码，然后将其合并在一起，就所有那些东西
and just that whole notion of being able to kind of, you know, create code as a team and then merge it together and all of that
你们知道，切入到自己的功能分支或错误修复分支或诸如此类的任何东西
and you know break off into your own feature branches or bugfix branches or anything like anything like that
一般来说，对于软件工程来说非常重要，我倾向于制作大量关于实际编写代码的技术视频
really vital for soft engineering in general, I tend to make a lot of videos on the technicalities of actually writing code
但后来我意识到很多人问我，如果在一个团队中，这是如何工作的，如果我在一个团队中
but then I realize that a lot of people ask me, well how does this work if I'm in a team, right, if I'm in a team of people
我们在研究同个东西，这是如何工作的，因为所有的视频，我是唯一真正在研究它们的人
and we're all working on the same thing, how does this work, because all of my videos, I'm kind of the only one really working on them
正因为如此，就没有搞那些，而且因为我在教你们一些具体的东西，不会花太多时间在那儿
um and so because of that I don't, and and because I'm teaching you guys like a specific thing, I'm not spending too much time being like
如果这是在团队环境中，而不是我们应该做这个或那个
well if this was more in a team environment than we should do this or that
所以今天我想花点时间谈谈那个
so I want to spend a little bit of time kind of talking about that today as well
但希望我们可以对这些合并请求进行排序，这儿有7个打开的合并请求
but hopefully we can just kind of sort through these pull requests,  we have seven open pull requests
emmm，不要忘记Hazel的仓库链接在每个视频的描述中都有
um other right now, don't forget that the repository for Hazel is in the description of every video
如果你们有想改的代码，或注意到我犯了个错误，并且想修复它，那么一定要去看看那个
definitely check that out, if you have code that you want to change, or if you notice that I make a mistake and you want to fix it
或者你们想继续添加一些有用的内容，然后一定要去打开一个合并请求或问题哦
or you want to go ahead and just add something that you think is useful, then definitely open a pull request or an issue
因为至少我们会讨论这个，社区也会和你们讨论这个
because at the very least, we'll discuss this, and the community will discuss this with you
这样，在工作流过程中，你们就可以掌握所有信息
and then that way you can kind of get to grips with just you know the whole stuff when during workflow
以及如何共同构建这个项目，所以我对那些感到很是兴奋，让我们看看这些合并请求吧
and how we can build this project together, so I'm really excited for all of that, let's take a look at pull requests
那么我们有7个合并请求，这就是Hazel仓库，当然这是它的样子
so we have seven pull requests, this is the Hazel repository, of course this is what it looks like
应该有README的，我很快会添加一个
README wise, I'm going to add a README very very soon
这将有关于如何打开合并请求的信息，因为那些才是你们真正想要的东西
and this will have information on how to open pull requests, because those are those are really things that you want to have
为什么我们有两个分支，这是什么，所以我第一次注意到这个，老实说，我不知道那是什么
why do we have two branches, what's this, so first time I'm noticing this, to be honest, I have no idea what that is
无论如何，不是12月份，所以我们这里有一个README文件，将包含如何建造Hazel
not the December anyway whatever, so we have we had this README file here, which will contain information on things like how to build Hazel
以及如何提交合并请求以及如何提交问题和有关一般协作的信息
and how to submit pull requests and how to submit issues and just information about general collaboration
所以那通常是Github中放置此类信息的地方，我还没有这样做，但后面会做的
so that is usually a place in github where you would put such information, I haven't done that yet, but I will
但现在你们可以看到，我们有6个问题和一堆请求，其中一些你们可以看到非常频繁地出现
but for now you can see that we have six issues and a bunch of pull requests, and some of these you can see just coming in pretty frequently
通常我会线下看这些内容，因为很明显，我们每周都会收到越来越多的
and usually I will kind of read these offline, because obviously you know every week we get more and more of these
我不能每周都做一期，至少现在不行，我只是把每件事都做完了
and I can't make an episode every week, at least not at this point, where I kind of just go through everything
如果这是你们想在某个时候看到的，我现在告诉你们，这不会每周都发生
if that's something that you guys want to see at some point, I'm telling you right now, it's not gonna happen every week
但也许每个月，或者每两周，或者诸如此类的，如果你们想让我拍一段我喜欢的视频，好吧
but maybe every month or every two weeks or something like that, if you guys just want me to make a video where I'm like okay
让我们过滤掉所有这些问题和合并请求，然后我就可以做那些了
let's just filter through all of these issues and pull requests, then I can probably do that
但一般来说，当在火车上或其他时候，一有空余时间，我会在手机上看这个，并且回复
but in general I just you know, when I'm just on the train or something, and I have a spare moment I'll look at this on my phone and just reply
你们知道的，这是一种继续讨论的方式，所以那就是我现在处理这件事的方式
and just you know kind of kind of keep that discussion going, so that's how I kind of handle this stuff right now
因为很明显我没有时间坐在电脑前做这些事情
because obviously I don't really have the time to sit down at a computer and do all this stuff
因为我的生活很忙碌，所以至于合并请求，这就是我们今天看到的，所以让我们从头开始
because my life is just hectic anyway, so pull requests, this is what we're looking at today, so let's start from the beginning
实际上我们已经关闭了6个，我相信，我甚至喜欢这一个，使用唯一指针而不是原始指针
we've actually got six of them closed already I believe, I like even for this one, using unique pointers instead of raw pointers
是的，就像你们看到的，我对此做出了回应，不管怎样，我很久以前就做出了回应
yeah like you can see that I responded to this, two thumbs down, anyway I responded to this quite a while ago actually
我甚至举了一些例子，你们知道，也给出了些理由解释为什么我决定以那种方式去做
and I even gave some examples, and I you know gave some reasoning as to why I decided to do what I did a certain way
所以你们知道，就好比合并请求，实际上似乎没有任何作用，我也不知道为什么没有变化
so you know you know, this is like a pull request, that actually doesn't even seem to do any, ok, so does I don't know why the falls change is zero
但也许那个项目早已经关闭了，不重要了，关键是，这是一种独立的合并请求，对吧
but maybe that project and closed already, doesn't matter, the point is, this is kind of the sperate pull request, right
就像你们知道的那样，做了这个，很明显会创建个问题，并询问这样做是否合理
like you know, you know done this, and that obviously could have opened an issue instead, and asked if this was reasonable to do
或者如果那是我们的方向，但这也很好，我不介意做这样的事情，然后你们可以看到
or if that's the direction we're going in, but this is also fine, I don't mind doing something like this, and then you can see that
人们直接加入我们的讨论，然后如果我，你们知道的，我不喜欢什么，或者我想进一步讨论
people just jump in and we have a discussion going, and then if I you know don't like something, or if I want to discuss it further
然后我告诉你们怎么做，我的意思是我甚至喜欢把cn.cppreference和里面的东西联系起来
then I will kind of you know do this, and I mean I even like linked the cppreference and stuff inside in cases
所以这是一个很好的，对每个人来说都是一个很好的，有点像我们的课程
so it's kind of a good, it's kind of a good, kind of like us lesson for everyone
呃，实际上不太像课程，就像我不想以正确的方式
uh not not actually like lesson, like I'm not trying to be like my ways the correct way
这或多或少比人们可能没有想到的一些方面
it's more or less than in terms of like some uh aspects of this that people might not have thought about
这是一种终身教育，就像跳进这个讨论并参与进来一样
it's educational forever on the kind of just jump into this discussion and participate
所以我喜欢它，当人们经常这样做的时候，你们可以看到这一个里有六个不同的按钮
so I like it, when people do that a lot you can see six different people buttons fed in this one specifically
嗯，然后我甚至没有关闭合并请求，所以我不是像按钮一样完成，就是关闭了
um and then I didn't even close you know the pull request, so it's not like I'm just like button done, that's it closed
不，原来的创建者曾经关闭了合并请求，我想他们满意了，没关系
no the original poster close the pull request once, I guess they were satisfied that, that's fine
所以，这对那些真正想学习如何加入团队并编写引擎的人来说真的很好
so again this is really good for those of you for those of you who actually want to learn how to be on a team and write an engine
所有这些，而不仅仅是观看视频和复制代码，并尝试自己做所有事情
and all of that instead of just watching the videos and copying down the code, and trying to do everything yourself
认真地说，真的很酷，很可靠，它会给你们更多的团队经验
jump into this, seriously, it's really cool, it's solid, it's gonna give you much more of a team kind of experience
是的，我的意思是我来这里只是为了帮助你们
and yeah I mean I'm here to just help you guys out
你们会遇到很多这样的情况，嘿，Cherno，你完全错了
and again there's gonna be so many cases of you guys being like, hey cherno, you're completely wrong in this
这是正确的方式，或者这是更好的方式，我会像哦，伙计，谢谢你们给我指出来
this is the right way to do it, or this is a better way to do it, and I'll be like oh man, like thank you so much for showing me
我不会像哦，你们怎么敢的，像这个软件工程社区最糟糕的事情一样
I'm not gonna be like oh how dare you, like the worst thing about this software engineering community
这是一种编程社区，很多时候人们都很喜欢优越感，只是拒绝听取其他人的意见
this is kind of programming community, a lot of the time does the people just get very very like superior, and just refuse to listen to everyone else
而且认为每个人都在他们之下，我绝对不是那种人，老实说，我讨厌那些人
and think everyone's beneath them, I'm definitely not one of those people, I hate those people to be honest
我希望他们会更好，但关键是这就像是一个安全的空间
and I wish that they would be better, but the point is this is like a safe space
我的意思是，我会在整个系列中学到很多东西，所以你们让我们在友好环境中一起构建这个
like I mean I'm gonna learn a lot throughout this series, so you guys let's build this thing together in a nice friendly environment
是的，好吧，不管怎样，这只是我们可以做的一个例子，一般来说，合并请求是如何完成的
yeah okay, so anyway, that was just kind of an example of what we can kind of do, so or like how pull requests in general are done
所以不管怎样，我会看到我对这个项目的支持，这个项目很大
so anyway, I'd see my support of the project, this one's huge
不知道我今天是否会倾向于这个项目，因为它有17名参与者
I don't know if I'll tend to this one today, because it's got 7 17 participants
我想我确实在某个时候回答过这个，即使是Gaztin，我Discord的管理者，也回答了这个
and I did I think I think I did reply to this at some point, well even Gaztin who's an administrator on my discord replied to this
说我用premake代替CMake，这有点多余，还有很多其他的东西
and said that I'm using premake instead of CMake, and it's kind of redundant, and there's a lot of other stuff here
但是你们可以看到这个已经关闭了，所以是的，四天前的事，你们知道的，就是premake
but you can see this has been closed yet, so yeah and this stuff from like even four days ago, and you know he's premake blah blah
所以，是的，我对此不确定，我可能会暂时保持开放，这也是第一个问题
so yeah I'm not sure about this,  I might I'll keep that open for now, and it was the very first issue as well
这是第一个合并请求，很有趣，所以我们来看看
which is the very first support request, which is interesting, so yeah we'll take a look at that
好的，添加对该项目的linux支持，这很有雄心，我想我不确定这是否是最新的
okay, add linux support of the project, that's quite ambitious, I guess I'm not sure how up to date this is
你们可以看到它有冲突，这意味着它不是最新的
you can see it's got conflicts, which means it's not up to date
但是，添加对linux的支持，使文件更改全局艺术修复编译时代
but so add a support for linux, premake file change global art fix the compile era
是的，我的意思是，很明显，我很高兴像ben这样我不知道为什么是一样的，因为平台
yeah I mean like I'm obviously, I'm happy for like this to ben I'm not sure why it's the same, because the platforms over
是的，就像确定的那样，好了，当然
yeah so like certain, okay, sure
你能更新这个分支并确保它准备好合并了吗，我很乐意将它合并到主分支
can you please update this branch and make sure it's ready to merge, I'd be keen to merge this in
我甚至会加上一张笑脸，这是非常有点笑脸，是的，我不想完全不高兴
and I'll even add a smiley face, that's very is there a slightly smiley face, yes I don't want to be like full unhappy yet
但我会说，好了，像你们知道，让我们这样做，好了，用premake属性替换编译器标志
but I'll just yeah, okay, done, say so like this is you know, let's do this, okay, I replace compiler flags with premake properties
所以我必须在premake中用运行库的属性，所以我想我相信已经这样做了
so I have to premake file with properties for the runtime library, yes, so I think I've already done that I believe
因为我认为这里的情况是，当我们使用MDd和所有这些东西时，现在确信已经做了
so because I think what the thing here was that yeah back, when we used mdd and all of that stuff, I believe that right now
如果我们查看premake文件，我相信我们不会再这样做了，对吧，是的，我们用了runtime
if we look at the premake file, I believe we're not doing that anymore, right, yes we're doing runtime
我们没有像你们知道的MTd那样做，顺便说一句，我之所以要检查，不是因为
and we're not doing like you know MTd or anything like that, the reason I had to check, by the way, is not because
我太笨了，我记不起我们做了什么，做了什么，只是有时候
I'm that stupid that I can't remember what we did and what we did, and it's just sometimes like
我的意思是我有一个Hazel开发分支，开放给赞助人的，在那里我做了很多这类来的
I mean I have a Hazel development branch, that's excessible to patrons, where I do a lot of this kind of development stuff
有时我不记得我为开发分支做了什么，所有我在直播视频中做过的
and sometimes I don't remember what I've done kind of for that development branch, all of the stuff that I've actually done live in a video
所以那就是为什么有时候我只需要再检查一遍，好吧，不管怎样，最近已经做了，不行
so that's why sometimes I just need to double check, okay, anyway, so this this has been done recently not enough
过时了，谢谢你的建议，好吧，酷，我们开始吧，启动项目，现在我想这是我想做的
I'll just say obsolete, thanks for the suggestion, okay, cool, so there we go, start project, now I think this is something that I want to do
premake在哪里，因为我们没有启动项目，我知道有一个premake标志，就是startproject
where's that premake park, because we don't have a start project, I know that there's a premake flag for that, it's called startproject
所以startproject看起来真的很好，不错，不可能做出通用的不，不，我真的没有找到那个
so that looks really good at a start project, let's thumbs that up, it's not possible to make a universal no not really, I don't really find that
我看不太清楚，这很好，看看这个，看看这个讨论
I don't see that exactly, this is good see, look at this look at this discussion
人们正在就如何使这一行代码变得更好进行讨论，好像这太棒了，太棒了
people are having a nice discussion about maybe making this one line of code better, like that's fantastic, so really good
显然，在这种情况下，我们不需要这样做，而且甚至不能这样做
obviously in this case we don't need to do that, and we can't even do that
因为不管怎样，很清楚的一点是，只需要从项目中创建Sandbox
because yeah it's pretty clear anyway to just make Sandbox out of project
我很高兴，我现在就要把这个合并进来，所以我合并合并请求
I'm happy with that, I'm going to merge this in right now, so I merge pulled requests
我不喜欢这个合并的标题，不是吗，我肯定我很喜欢那个更多一点
yeah I don't like the this is the title of the of the merge, isn't it, I'm sure I like this that much
但是，我想Github只是喜欢这样做，所以我们将其合并，好了，现在合并了
but yeah I guess github just likes doing that way, so we'll just merge that in, okay, that's now merged
如果转到Github中的代码，可以看到我的最新提交是22秒前的合并请求
if you go to the code in github, you can see that my latest commit was merged pull request 22 seconds ago
如果我们也从这里开始，你们可以看到，这是一个提交，所以现在这个人也贡献了Hazel
if we look at the commence here as well, you can see that, there's that commit, so now this person is also contributed to Hazel
这真的很酷，而且我们也得到了，已经完成了这个，所以现在可以标记验证，好了
which is really cool, and also we get the you know we get this code done, so I can now kind of pull that verified, okay
不管怎样，我甚至不知道这意味着什么，但不管怎样，显然可以把这些拉到本地仓库中
whatever I don't know what that even means, but anyway I can now obviously pull the changes into my local depository
我会把它放在那里，所以我甚至可以告诉你们怎么做，以防你们不知道
and I will have that there, so I might even show you guys how to do that, so just in case you're unaware
所以我现在要做的就是拉取，我不知道我有没有什么东西，我可能会检出一些东西
so all I need to do now is just pull, I don't know if I've got any kind of stuff, I probably do have checkout stuff
我不知道为什么这么做，啊，这只是我做的，没有提交这个，哦，我一定没有提交这个
I don't know why I do actually, ah this is just did, I not commit this, maybe I didn't commit this, oh I must not have committed this
哦，那太棒了，好吧，有时候我也忘了提交，真需要在屏幕上贴便条，这样就可以提交了
oh that's fantastic, okay, sometimes I forget to commit code as well, I really need to put a post note on my monitor, so that I can commit stuff
但我们现在就把这些提交了，那么需要什么，我想就那样，对了，剩下什么，我不需要了
but let's just commit that stuff now, so what do we need that, and that I think that's it, right, what else is left, I don't need that
好了，我的意思是，我们实际上也可以这样做，所以我们要做什么，我们在Core.h中添加
okay, well I mean we might as well commit this actually, so what do we do, we added what was that in Core.h we had
因此，如果开启了调试，并且实际上第一件事，那就是对静态库所做的事情
so if if debugs on and am I actually the first thing on my right for the message is what we did regarding the static library
因此，我们已经链接动态库，我希望提交消息非常准确，所以你们可以现场看到
so we now link the dynamic library instead of well, I like to get my commit message is pretty accurate, so you'll see this live
它就是其中的运行库，是的，就是MDd，现在动态链接运行库，并定义那个
it's just called the runtime libraries in it, yeah Multi-thread dll, now linking runtime library dynamically, and define that
好吧，git push，虽然也需要拉取，我希望我先拉，没关系，已经提交了，这应该比较轻松
okay, git push, while we also need to pull, I wish I pulled first, it doesn't matter, we've committed it, this should be an easy match
然后也可以推送，所以要把它完成，很酷，你们看到我在这里直播做一些事情，这很酷
and then we can also push, so I'm just gonna get that done, it's like cool, you guys are seeing me do some stuff alive here, which is pretty cool
不管怎样，现在完成了，如果我们刷新仓库，应该看到这个，它可能必须合并，我做了一点
anyway, now that's done, if we were freshmester pository, we should see this, and it probably had to merge, yeah I did a little
我做了一个小小的合并，因为在我做最新的合并之前，我和它进行了提交，所以有点有趣
I did a little merge, because I and it up committing before I pulled the latest merge that we did, so that was a little bit fun there
但不管怎样，已经完成了，很酷，显然已经结束了，下一个依赖项位于解决方案文件夹中
but anyway, that's done now, cool, that's closed obviously, next one dependencies in a solution folder
我将所有依赖项组合在一个解决方案文件夹中，以减少混乱，太棒了
I grouped all the dependencies together in a solution folder for less cluttering, that's awesome
其实我很长时间都在想如何做到这一点，我想你们只是把它分成一组，是了，我真的很喜欢
I was actually wondering for a long time how to do that, I guess you just put it into a group, yeah I really like that
我肯定会更频繁地使用组，但总的来说这很好，所以这只是在文件末尾添加新行，没关系
I'll definitely be using groups more often, but in general this is good, so this is just adding a new line at the end of the file, that's fine
很好，我喜欢，所以我要合并，嗯，不，我不能，好了，酷
yeah that's pretty good, I like that, so I'm gonna merge that, um no, I can't, okay, cool
我不能，因为刚刚更新了premake，好吧，修复首次构建失败，现在先检查目录是否存在
I can't because I just updated the premake file myself,okay, fixed build failing first time, um now first check folder exist
看起来是不是很复杂，好吧，酷，实际上如果不存在的话，是个好主意，我想还有一个
doesn't this look very fold, okay, cool, actually if not exist, yeah that's good, that's a good idea, there was also another one I think
这与此相关，我不确定哪一个更好，但这是修改了Hazel项目的后置构建命令
which was related to that, I'm not sure which one's better, but it's postbuild command for Hazel project modified
这显示xcopy将知道参数是一个目录，并且在一个文件上
this one show the xcopy will know that the argument to is a fold, and on a file
所以我不确定，但这是被引用的，所以不确定，比如为什么这个会引用这个，到底什么意思
so I'm not sure, but this it was referenced, so I'm not sure why, like why was this ref like he referenced this, right, so what does that mean exactly
哦，那是另一个，抱歉，那是9号，这是21号，好了，有几个，意思是这也是处理这个的
oh that's a different one, sorry, that's No.9, this is 21, okay, so there's been a few, mean, this what does this do this
这只是把它分开，所以这不是一个参数，这是真的，但我不确定这样是否能解决它
this just splits it up, so that this is instead of one argument, it's true, but I'm not sure if that like does that fix it
好了，让我们快速打开目录，这样我们就有了，这样就可以删除bin了
okay, let's quickly reopen this, so we have, so the idea is we can delete bin
如果我们尝试构建Sandbox，第一次就会失败，因为文件夹还不存在
and then if we try and build Sandbox, it will fail the first time, because the folder doesn't exist yet
所以，让我们看看我们现在是否真的可以解决这个问题，因为真的很烦人，我同意
so let's see if we can actually fix this right now, because yeah that's really annoying I agree
好了，就是这样，这失败了，我讨厌所有这些，所有这些警告
okay, so there it is, it's failed over here, I hate all of this, all of these warnings
真的需要屏蔽它们或类似的东西，因为我认为很好
really need to suppress them or something like that, because I think that think that they're fine
我想他们只需要感到惊讶，但不管怎样，那么错误在哪里，就在那里，所以命令失败了
I think that they just need to be surprised, but anyway, okay, so where's the error, there it is, so command blah blah, failed
让我们试试，试着做这个，那么复制这个，然后到premake文件，就是这儿，粘贴这个
so let's try, let's try do this instead, so I'm just going to copy this, and then go to the premake file, there it is, paste this instead
然后我们需要，需要做什么，我们需要回到这里，离开bin
and then we need to, what do we need to do, we need to go back here, we need to leave bin
我们需要重新启生成项目，可以把startproject放在workspace中
we need to regenerate the projects,  I'm able to set startproject should be in one space
哦，好吧，也许我不应该合并，然后就是startproject Sandbox，为什么会失败
oh okay, well maybe I shouldn't have merged, then startproject Sandbox, why was that a failure
好了，让我想到了另一点，很明显理想情况下，在实际合并之前，应该先测试合并请求
okay, this brings me to another point obviously ideally, you should definitely test the pull request before you actually merge them in
我有一种感觉，因为这是自动合并的
I have a feeling that because this was automatically merged it
所以它是在Hazel项目Sandbox之前完成的，有趣，我不确定之后是否需要完成，但不确定
so it was done before Hazel stop project Sandbox, that's interesting, I'm not sure maybe needs to be done after, but I'm not sure
我的意思是，很明显就像我想象的那个人测试过它
I mean,obviously like I imagined that this guy tested it
但我们可以，再运行一遍，无法设置startproject
but we can, let's just run that again, unable to set startproject
project应该在？中，所以它在project范围内，这可能是因为我们包含了这些内容
and project scope should be in work, okay, so it's in a project scope, that's probably because we've included this stuff
好了，很酷，所以这需要在workspace内完成，所以也许我会在这里完成
okay, cool, so this needs to be done in the workspace scope, so maybe I'll do it up here
让我们再试一次，好的，我们开始了，把它移到那里，那很有意义
so let's try this again, okay, there we go, so we'll move it there, that makes sense
因为你们可以立即在架构中看到启动项目，所以一切都很好
because you immediately see the start of project in the architecture, everything's fine
好了，好了，现在我们已经完成了，我们要确保这儿没有bin目录
okay, cool, so now that we've done that, we'll make sure that the case there's no bin fold
让我们尝试构建Sandbox，看看它是否再次失败，不确定它是否会失败，不，真没失败
let's try and build Sandbox, and let's see if it fails again, I'm not sure if it will, no, it didn't really
在那里构建得非常快，让我们删除这个，然后再试一次，好吧，我不相信
that built very quickly there, let's delete this, and let's try again, all right, I don't buy it
开始了，成功了，好了，很酷，所以拆分文件才是真正的解决方案，我更喜欢它的原因
okay, there we go, that succeeded, okay, cool, so splitting out the file was really the solution, the reason I like that better
好吧，那太棒了，所以我喜欢这个比另一个好得多，因为那个需要更多的代码，对吧
so, okay, that's brilliant, so the reason I like this a lot better than the other one like because this this is more code, right
所以这必须做更多它必须做的，如果不存在的，但是这就像是一对额外的字符
so this has to do more it has to do,  and if not exist, blah blah blah, but this is like, it's this, it's literally just like a couple extra characters
只需将路径拆分为文件夹，将实际的拆分为目录和文件，真的很好，因为它有一个长路径
just splitting up the path into the folder, and the actual like into the directory and the file, which is really good is it having like one big path
所以我真的很高兴，我觉得这样好多了，事实上我甚至都不知道
so I'm really happy with that, I think that's a lot better, actually I don't even know it like
所以那是第一个参数，然后我们有很多复制的途径，我猜是从，然后Sandbox，我不知道
so that's the first argument, then we have the a lot of pathway we're copying from, I guess from, and then wearing two Sandbox, I don't know
总之，重点是把它分成两个参数
anyway well, the point is splitting it often to into two arguments
那似乎解决了问题，我真的很喜欢这个解决方案，所以我要，我要做我经常做的了
that seems to fix it, I really like this fix, so I'm going to, I'm going to do my classic
请更新它，这样我就可以合并它了，因为我可以自己提交，但我想给这个家伙一点信任
please update it, so I can merge it, because I could commit it myself, but I kind of want to give this guy credit for doing it
因为那是一个困扰我很久的问题，所以我们会给他一个机会来解决它
because yeah this was an issue that's been bothering me for ages, so we'll give him a chance to fix it
我们会给他几天的时间来更新，然后我想做的一件事就是这个，可以看到
we'll give him like a couple days to update it, and then also one thing I want to do is this, I will see that
好了，酷，所以这就是第九号方案
so blah blah, okay, cool, so this is the one that solution plantation version No.9
我如何引用另一个问题，啊，我们开始吧，好了，我有正确的链接
how do I reference another issue, ah here we go, okay, I have that links properly
它应该，我不知道，如果它想在那里有一个空格，但不管怎样，好吧，酷，关闭它，出来吧
it should, I don't know, if it wants a space there, but whatever, okay, cool, so close and come out
很明显，我引用了这个，好吧，酷，好了，一切都完成了，我真的很高兴我们做到了
and then that's obviously I reference this, and okay, cool, so there we go, that's everything done, I'm really glad we did that
因为我们修复了启动项目，修复了文件夹复制的问题，还做了什么，我想就是那些
because we fixed up the starter project, we fixed that folder thing copying um, and what else do we do, I think that was about it
但不管怎样，我带你们看了整个工作流，所以现在我们有了解决所有问题的权限
but anyway, I kind of took you guys through the whole workflow, so now that we have we permission to address everything
这是一个正在进行的讨论，我想我最终会关闭它，因为CMake我不认为
this is kind of an ongoing discussion that I think I'll close eventually, because CMake I don't think
我仍然不确定CMake支持是否应该成为Hazel的一个需要，仅仅因为premake存在
I'm still not sure if CMake support should ever be a thing in Hazel, just because premake exists
还有premake，我想无论如何都可以生成CMakefiles
and also premake, I think can generate CMakefiles, anyway
所以和premake相比，不管怎样，它比我的观点要好的多，
so and premake, it just 1000 times better than see making my opinion, anyway,
至于这个Linux支持，我很乐意确保它能正常运行
linux support, again, I'd be happy to kind of make sure that works
但我可能想先在Linux虚拟机或其他上测试它，然后再测试我们已经解决的其他问题
but I wanted to probably test that on a Linux VM or something first, and then everything else we've addressed
所以那就是所有的合并请求，希望这种在打开合并请求时有意义
so that's all the pull requests, hope that kind of makes sense as far as opening pull requires
真的很简单，所要做的就是拷贝Hazel，对吧，这样就可以把它拷贝到自己的账号
really easy all you have to do is kind of fork Hazel, right, so you can fork it into your own kind of into your own account
完成后，你们可以在分支中或仅在仓库主分支中（仓库副本）做想做的
and then once you've done that, you can do what you want in a branch or just in your master in kind of your copy of the repository
一旦你们完成了，就可以去合并请求，新的合并请求
and then once you've done that, you can just go to pull request, new pull request
然后可以将副本合并到我的副本中，对吧，就是那样，这将展示所有的差异，一切都有
and then you can merge you know your copy into my copy, right, and that's it, and this will show you all the difference, and everything will be
你们知道，买一辆cherno车，会觉得很顺利，不管怎样，没关系，你们不会明白那个笑话的
you know, bought a cherno as one might see really smooth is the idea, anyway, it doesn't matter, you guys won't get that joke
但关键是你们可以创建一种合并，就可以看到它是如何运行的，一旦我更新了README
but the point is you can kind of create that merge that in, and you can see that's kind of how it works, I will once I do update that README file
我会有一种更好的格式，让你们知道应该如何组织你们的信息
I will have more or less like a better kind of like a format for like how you should structure your messages
你们应该在这里提供什么信息，因为现在就像你们知道的一样
and what information you should provide here, because right now it's kind of just like you know right whatever
但我希望将来能更有条理，是的，就是那样，希望有意义
but I would like that to be more structured in the future, yeah, that's about it, hope that made sense
好了，那就是Github中的合并请求，可以看到这有多大的帮助，以及现在可以做什么
alright, so that is pull requests in Github, you can see how helpful that is, and how we can kind of just for now
这真的像是小改动小修复，因为一开始就没有太多的事情要做
it's really like small changes small fixes, because there isn't too much to Hazel to begin with
但一旦我们了大量的代码，仓库非常庞大，这儿就会有很多东西
but once we have you know massive, massive like amount of code, and our code base is just huge, there'll be so many things here
在那儿，人们可以改进、修复并实施，因此构建请求显然是在以后要做的
and there that people can improve and fix, and implement as well, so build requests obviously going into the future
如果我们能像现在这样开始加速，那就太好了
if we can kind of start ramping that up like as it is right now, that's perfect
我们可以构建它，确保人们对此感到满意
we can establish it, we can make sure that people are comfortable with that
因为在将来，那将非常重要，希望你们喜欢这期视频
because in the future, that's gonna be really important, hope you guys enjoyed this video
如果你们还没有为它点赞的话，还可以通过访问patreon.com/thecherno帮助支持该系列
if you didn't hit that like button, you can also help support the series by going over to patreon.com/thecherno
非常感谢所有使本系列成为可能的小伙伴，如果你们支持的话，就会提前一周收到视频
huge thank you as always to all the patreons that make this series possible, if you guys support there, you'll get videos a week early
以及访问Hazel私有开发库，在那里你们可以看到我写的所有代码
as well as access to that private Hazel development repository, where you can see like all the code that I've done
这远远领先于这个仓库，所以那真的很酷，非常感谢你们帮助支持这个系列
which is far more ahead of this kind of repository, so that's really cool, and a little kind of thank you for helping to support this series um
下次我想我们可能会继续开发Hazel
next time I think we're gonna probably move on with actual Hazel development
这段时间我想做的就是输入和按键编码之类的东西
one thing that I wanted to do for a while is like input and keycodes and stuff like that
所以我们可以做那个，是的，我们可能会搞那个，我想是的，直到下次，再见
so we can kind of do that, yeah, we'll probably end up doing that I think so until next time, goodbye